The Clover Kingdom.
In this place where magic is everything,
there lives one boy who was born without it.
His name is Asta.
His strength and determination helped him become a magic knight.
And despite the many challenges he faces,
he aims for the top and refuses to give up.
Rich or poor, royalty or commoner,
Asta believes anyone can shine.
His mission is to prove that to the whole world.
And to become the next Wizard King.
Your Majesty!
You know your wandering privileges are suspended!
I didn't think you'd find me if I went this way.
Do you have any idea how many years I've been serving you?
Now please go back to your office and take care of that mountain of paperwork.
But I already handled everything for today.
What?
I understand your concern, Marx.
It's important to keep up with reports and all.
But to really get to know my people, I need to come out and walk among them.
Please, wait!
I wish I could let you go, sir.
But with that devil and spade threatening us, the risk is just too great.
Yes, that's true.
I still only have a fraction of my magic power, so there isn't much I can do at the moment.
Well then, I have a few favors to ask of you, Marx.
You're about to be very busy.
You're about to be busy.
I'm not too busy.
I need to be busy.
God, let's be busy.
If you are busy.
I don't want to be busy.
I'm not too busy.
And so I'm busy.
Wow
Yeah
, Yeah
High, low, lowancy
We're all on top and down
in the end
We believe in today
too
And both are
I bet there
Now are
small
Have you
möchten
There's another time to change the time
I believe the new hiccos will disappear
Even if the Eevees will change again
We believe that we Digital
You see that, the Wooo is a new one
What aNe анность is
That's nothing
All things
Go on
Hi people
look
I saw how it can happen
Nah
sheets
今
ポング
君と High
heard
Türk
ً
Oh
Okay, Asta get ready right water creation magic see dragons water ball
Go go go
Need to fight harder you can't hold back just because this is practice
All right fine, but you better not cry water creation magic
See dragon
Train for six months then we will fight together to stop magicula
We're not there. We haven't trained enough
Oh
You blocked it. You're no fun
What it's Sally good to see you Asta. How's it going?
Why are you here?
Don't tell me you escaped nah, I wish mr. Mushroom head over there brought me to visit
I'd prefer it if you didn't call me that. Oh, yeah, that's the wizard king's assistant
And some other guy makasa from the magic item research lab
Huh you can make magic items
Yes, his majesty was impressed by sally's knowledge of magical science
So he asked her to invent an item that would give us an edge in the battle that's coming up
I have my reservations, but
Okay, first off i'm gonna need some baseline data
So I'll just experiment on the two of you in your dreams
Even if you have turned over a new leaf only an idiot would agree to that
Let's go
Did you really have to rip your shirt off?
I gave you my word
After the last fight I said do what you want to me
I'm so glad you remember that
Just try not to do anything that hurts super bad. Okay
So you'll let her take all your organs as long as she numbs you first you might want to rethink that
Organ removal she wouldn't right if things get too gory we may have to pull the plug on the whole endeavor
Now let's do it
Actually here's a better idea i'm gonna save you for last asta huh?
Well the thing I want to make is supposed to increase mana output and you don't have any to speak of
Which means I should probably start with you
Look I don't want anything to do with this at all
I'm royalty and even if I wasn't I would still say no
By the way are your squad mates here?
They're out assignments and training and all that but most of them should be back by now
Oh I guess they're here
Oops I forgot I have a thing
I should throw this out
Hey look at the time
Lucky me so many test subjects
Hey stop
Come back
You need our permission to do that and you don't have it
Look the wizard king
Listen to me you two forget about us just stop her right now
Wow we're on it
Okay I think I'm far enough away now
I'm not letting that psycho science chick lay a finger on me
Awww
Put me down right now you are so dead
Aww but when I create this new magic item it's gonna make you a lot stronger
So don't you think you should help me out dumb gloss punk
If you have to insult me can you not do it in shorthand
So glass punk uses flame magic
Stop making a shooter dammit
Which means the dark magic equation should yield a mana exponent of
I know the perfect formula
And now using sticky salamander as a temporary trial subject
Observe
What the hell's happening there's so much mana burning inside me I feel like I might melt
I know pretty great huh
Uh oh this is way too much make it stop or I'm gonna
Blow a fuse
Huh I'm guessing that means the dark magic equation is still incomplete
Maybe the liquid's too concentrated
Got some data though
Let's keep working
No need to be scared
I won't dissect you guys
Transformation magic
Hang on don't attack her
Why what is it
Oh wow that's Marie
I don't want anyone to harm my precious angel
You do know that's not her right ghost
She's made of goo
Goo or no goo that's still her face
Are you ready
You guys use combination magic together
So I wanted to test you simultaneously
You're pairing yourself that's so amazing
Come on Vanessa
You said you'd restrain yourself
Oh but this is a rare vintage I may never see again
That's obviously a trap
Can we please get out of here
Now the next experiment
A tempting trail of cupcakes
Wonder if it leads to pastry paradise
Too easy
Say no Vanessa you have to
She told you it was a trap
Fenrul and Vanessa
You guys okay?
Yeah why did something happen?
Meow
It looks like we got here too late
We can't let Sally hurt anybody else
Good food everywhere
Ugh none of my tests have been going the way that I planned
I need more data to work with
Hold it
Charmy say something
Asta what gives?
You're supposed to be the last one
Did you get tired of waiting?
Hey!
I won't go back on my word
You can do what you want to me
But leave my teammates alone
You should go back on your word
Otherwise this lunatic is gonna chop you to bits
We owe her
She's the reason we made it to the capital
Because of Sally's group
We managed to save our friends
That's why I have to keep my promise to her
Good boy
It's important to be a man of your word
Please give me something to knock me out
Oh this won't hurt a bit
You'll barely feel it
Here you go
What's up?
It's all mine now
I can culture it later
What?
All you wanted was my hair?
Weird
Well yeah
Don't you remember what you said?
That I could experiment all I wanted
As long as I didn't harm anybody
But in the end
I guess I did cause them a lot of distress, huh?
Don't worry
They'll all be back to normal soon
Their mana just got cranked up to the max
And their bodies kind of shut down
Wow, Sally
Crazy or not
You still kept up your end of the deal
Actually, you know something?
I don't think I can get by with just your hair
How about some nail clippings too?
Sure, I don't mind
That's not how you clip someone's nails
While I'm at it
Do you mind if I draw your blood?
It's all in the name of science
And I might as well take your heart, lungs, and eyeballs too
Take the hair and get lost!
Test away!
If your research helps people, I'm all for it!
That was rough
I'm so glad it's over now
Time for a little payback
You sick freak!
Calm down, guys
Everyone's better now
Let's just move past it
As for the data that was gathered
Wow
I don't understand this at all
But it's fascinating
Makozo will investigate these findings at the lab
After that, the magic item will be created
Do your best, science guy
And you work hard too, Sally
Okay!
We've got this!
Well, at least they got some solid data
Let's hope that it does some good
You better not screw this up
If you do, then you're dead
What are you waiting for?
Use your spatial magic and send them on their way
Uh, right
Why is she bossing me around?
Let's head back, Sally
Coming!
Research that helps people
Huh
Maybe he's onto something
Good luck!
See you soon!
I hope you're right, Asta
We're close to Arendam Village
It's odd that you and I were sent together
Since we're captains of two different squads
I don't care how strange it is
My goal is to find anyone who dares threaten our kingdom and strike them down
What could have caused the crisis in this village?
Your majesty, I've brought the two magic night captains you called for
Sorry to take you away from your squads when you're so busy
No, it's fine
What's wrong, sir?
Have either of you heard tell of a place called Arendam Village?
It's in the Forsaken Realm
I happened upon it while I was out wandering
I mean investigating different areas of the Clover Kingdom
According to several reports, Arendam Village has begun to suffer from a bandit problem recently
Then we should send a team there to deal with them
No, that won't be enough to solve this
I'm not sure why, but I have a feeling that something unfavorable is going on
The only question is what?
Something unfavorable?
Sounds ominous
That's where you two come in
You'll disguise yourselves and mingle with the villagers
Perhaps that way you'll learn something useful about the bandits
It's an undercover investigation
Sounds like he's thought this through
Are these really our disguises?
Listen, I hate to criticize, but this only makes us look more suspicious
These outfits are our only hope
We don't know how to conduct ourselves like commoners
So our best strategy is to hide our appearance altogether
Some nobles do forsake their lives of luxury
Perhaps people will assume that's the case with us
Right, that makes sense
Anyway, where should we begin gathering intel?
The village square is as good a place as any
Perfectly sound, and lest we forget
The Wizard King said we're supposed to act casual
So let's do our best to blend in
Blending in isn't their strong suit
Maybe if they could relax we'd be able to pull it off
But I mustn't overstep my station
What happened here?
We knew there were areas that hadn't been restored yet
But this is true devastation
It's unspeakable
We'll have time to address this matter eventually
We need to focus on the mission at hand
I'll go this way
I'll try here
Pardon me
Hello there, I don't believe we've met before
I'm Leon, I'm a traveling mage
Yes, and the same goes for me
My name's Mark
Traveling mages, eh?
We heard about the bandits that target this place
And we'd like you to tell us everything you know
So that we can protect ourselves
I don't know Jack
Why don't you go bother somebody else?
I've never seen guys like those before
They're wary of us because of these so-called disguises
What should we do?
I mean, Leon?
Oh, yes
If you three run into any trouble while you're there
There's a special word you can say that'll probably clear it out
Crono
Vala
Huh?
You're kidding
No way
I can hardly believe it
Are you friends of Crono Vala?
That old woman was a huge help to our village
One time when business was really slow
She rustled off a ton of customers for me
Man, I made a fortune that day
But then suddenly she disappeared
So how's that sweet little lady been doing?
Crono Vala
Wait
Crono
Nova Crono
I get it
When his majesty wandered out here that was the alias he used
You guys know Crono Vala?
Everyone loves her
Here, take this
All my fields were destroyed a while back so I can't offer you much
I couldn't possibly take it for free
Will this cover it?
What?
All this Yule?
Forget the carrot, this much would buy you my whole inventory
Go ahead and keep the rest
Use it to help restore the village
You sure that's okay?
That's crazy
I wonder who they are
Apparently they're friends of Crono Vala's
Hmm
King Julius is amazing
They respect him so deeply without even knowing it's him
So much for not drawing attention to ourselves while we're in town
Hopefully he's doing a better job
Oh my goodness, do you know Crono Vala too, sir?
That incredible woman saved my sweet baby's life
Really?
I went into labor while I was out in the fields one day
And she called for a doctor to help me
I even named him Vala after her
Here, would you like to hold him?
Oh no, that's alright
I don't think I've held a baby since Noelle was this tiny
Nose
Nose?
Everyone here seems to know King
I mean Crono Vala
Yes, I've noticed
My name is Mayor and I'm the mayor of this village
There isn't much that we can offer you but we'd like to invite you gentlemen to stay for the night
Oh yeah, great idea! Stay with us!
Our food's in short supply but we can cook for you too!
What do you think?
We have no reason to decline
We were told we should mingle amongst the villagers
And this is the perfect chance
Well, I guess that's that then
In the end, we didn't learn anything about the bandit attacks
And it's not just that
We still don't know what unfavorable activity is going on here
What? What's happening?
I knew it
I think they're asleep
Let's go
Just as I thought
You must be the group of bandits that we've heard about
So what if we are?
Give us your money now
Unless you want to get hurt
Take them down
What? That can't be right
You did this?
I wish I could say that it came as a shock
It's over now, everyone
But, sir!
We knew this would happen
Even though we only did it so we could survive
After the Eye of the Midnight Sun attacked
Our village was left in shambles
We had hoped to receive aid from the royal capital
But no one ever came
So we were plunged even deeper into poverty than before
That being said, despite our intent to rebuild our village
We were still committing a terrible crime
I led my people to engage in this behavior
Therefore, I ask that you allow me to take all the punishment myself
You can't do that!
You were only trying to help us
I had no idea things were so dire
If we'd been quicker to address the problem, this wouldn't have happened
We can't let the mayor take the blame on his own
If you're going down, we're going down with you
No, you mustn't
This can't possibly be real
Lord Flegolion and Lord Nozel
Two of the Magic Knight Captains
You're obviously in need of our assistance
So we can overlook what you've done
There you go again, being too soft
They're bandits
They should be arrested and tried for their crimes
Well, I'd say you're being too harsh
I order you all to participate in the reconstruction of every village in this area
A crime is still a crime
And you must atone for what you've done
So we're forgiven?
I swear, the capital hasn't forsaken you
But it seems that we weren't entirely aware of your situation
We're going to make even greater strides to restore this kingdom, so please have faith in us
Thank you so much
That's everything we have to report from our time in Erendom
Great job, Captains! Seems like you made the right choice
We've sent some knights to the other villages
That way we can determine what sort of aid each one needs and how much
As Wizard King, my job, and yours as well, is to ensure that all of our people can live safely and peacefully
And now that you've spent some time with them, perhaps you've learned to see their situation in a new light
Of course
That's why he sent us
Captains, from now on, I want you to work even harder to lead the Magic Knights and protect this kingdom
Yes, your majesty
Don't let me down
Now that that's taken care of, I think I'll wander around by myself
Certainly not
No? Well, then I suppose I'll check in with Yami
I'll tell you, Marks, all this sitting around is driving me batty
I know you feel useless
But right now, the Clover Kingdom needs you more than you realize
Without me
諦めることも悪いことじゃないって あなたはいつも笑って言うけど 手を伸ばせば届くなら 紡いだ今までを 目駄にするわけにはいかない
何度だって悔やんで 何度だって歩く そのために 突き放されるから
正解のない旅をしよう 変わっていくことに 怖がる必要はないから
正解のない道上 そこではきっと一人じゃない
間違いを間違いで 終わらせないで
涙を涙で 拭わないで
確信がある その心を掛ける
ここならもう一人じゃない
次回アスターは またローマン公開けるよ
You